SEIF AMR

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

- 01/10/1995
- **1** +201128444403
- ✓ seifammar1125@gmail.com
- Cairo, Egypt

SKILLS

- HTML
- CSS
- Sass
- JavaScript
- ReactJs
- Vuejs
- git
- Java
- Laravel

EDUCATION

BACHELOR OF INFORMATICS AND COMPUTER SCIENCES

The British university in Egypt/London South Bank Universiity

2018 - 2014

PROFILE

4 years as a software developer seeks for joining teams as a Software developer providing Software solution which meets costumer needs in addition to ability to take a new development challenges and new technologies and tools Moreover Have the ability to work with teams and groups which translate UI/UX design wireframes to well designed ,Reusable and clean code .

WORK EXPERIENCE

SENIOR SOFTWARE ENGINEER

mar 2021 - Present

34 Media Labs

- Transforming wireframes and ui designs to fully clean reusable and funcional code
- build, test and maintain webapps and websites
- participate in Apis design and documentation
- fixing bugs and code revamping

TECHNICAL BUISSNESS ANALYST

jan 2021 - mar 2021

tanmeyah for microfinance services

- gather requirements from stakeholders
- · ensure projects technical feasability
- · collaborating in technical actions

DESKTOP DEVELOPER

jun 2018 - jul 2019

Gratsia Tours

 Building and maintaining desktop application for managing reservations and financials

PROJECTS

RAHET BALY

A VUE WEBAPP DESIGNED TO BE A FULL-FLEDGED SUPPORT PLATFORM FOR NEW MOTHERS. WE SUPPORT MOMS THROUGH A HUGE ARRAY OF PRODUCTS & SERVICES THAT MAKES THEIR LIVES EASIER. HEALTHIER & HAPPIER.

HTTPS://RAHETBALLY.COM

NEW AVENUE

HELPING CLIENTS FIND THE PERFECT HOME FOR THE PERFECT FIT THAT MEETS THEIR NEEDS TO FIND THE BEST DEALS FOR OUR CLIENTS, WITH THE OPTIMAL PAYMENT PLANS. HTTPS://NEWAVENUE-EGYPT.COM

TODO-LIST

REACT-BASED TODO LIST APPLICATION WITH THE ABILITY TO ADD TASKS, SAVE TASKS AS DRAFTS, AND MANAGE PROJECTS. TASKS CAN BE ASSIGNED TO PROJECTS AND SAVED IN THE DRAFTS SECTION.

HTTPS://SEIF1125.GITHUB.IO/TODO-LIST/

COLORS

IS A BEAUTY CHAIN THAT WAS BORN IN 2001. COLORS HELPS CUSTOMERS TO ACHIEVE THE PRESTIGIOUS LOOK AND THE AFFORDABLE INDULGENCE CAPITALIZING ON A WIDE PRODUCT PORTFOLIO AND A QUALIFIED TEAM OF IN HOUSE ADVISORS.

HTTPS://COLORSBEAUTY.COM

TIC-TAC-TOE

THIS IS A SIMPLE WEB-BASED TIC-TAC-TOE GAME BUILT USING REACT. THE GAME ALLOWS TWO PLAYERS TO PLAY THE CLASSIC GAME OF TIC-TAC-TOE IN A WEB BROWSER. IT INCLUDES BASIC FEATURES LIKE GAME STATUS, MOVE HISTORY, AND RESET FUNCTIONALITY.

HTTPS://SEIF1125.GITHUB.IO/TIC-TAC-TOE